A Finding Aid to the Federal Art Project, Photographic Division Collection, circa 1920-1965, bulk 1935-1942, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Federal Art Project, Photographic Division collection
circa 1920-1965
bulk 1935-1942
Archives of American Art
Federal Art Project. Photographic Division
AAA.fedeartp14
Archival Resource Key
12.4 Linear feet
The Federal Art Project, Photographic Division collection dates from circa 1920-1965, with the bulk of the records spanning the active years of the Federal Art Project (FAP), 1935-1942. The collection comprises 12.4 linear feet of mostly photographic prints and negatives that document primarily artwork produced by artists employed by the FAP. A smaller number of photographs also document other programs of the FAP, such as art classes and community centers, exhibitions by children and adults, artwork installed in public buildings, project divisions, and demonstrations of art processes by FAP artists.
Provenance
The collection was anonymously donated to the Archives of American Art in the late 1950s.
Related Material
Among the holdings of the Archives of American Art are related collections, including the Federal Art Project of the Work Projects Administration records, 1935-1948. Additional FAP records are held by the National Archives and Records Administration in Washington D.C.
Alternative Forms Available
This collection was digitized in its entirety in 2017 and is available via the Archives of American Art's website.
Restrictions on Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center. Contact Reference Services for more information.
Historical Note
The Federal Art Project (FAP) was one of the Depression-era work-relief programs of the Federal Works Progress Administration (WPA). The program was founded in August 1935 to provide employment for artists and to implement visual arts programs in local communities across the country.
Together with the Federal Music Project, the Federal Theater Project, and the Federal Writers' Project, the FAP formed part of the WPA's Federal Project No. 1. The WPA became the Work Projects Administration in 1939 when it fell under the administrative hand of the newly created Federal Works Agency; concurrently the Federal Art Project was officially re-named the Federal Art Program.
Under the direction of Holger Cahill, the goals of the FAP fell into three main areas: production of artwork, art education through art classes and community centers, and art research through the Index of American Design. During the course of the program, artists created murals and other works of art for many non-Federal government buildings such as schools, hospitals, and libraries. Separate photographic divisions were set up in several states, most notably in New York City, to document the work of artists employed by the program, activities in art education such as classes for children and adults, community center outreach programs, and other "Federal 1" projects, including the Federal Theater and Music Projects. Employees of the photographic division were also involved in other assignments, such as creating exhibitions and photo murals.
The Federal Art Project ended in 1943.
Scope and Content Note
The Federal Art Project (FAP), Photographic Division collection dates from circa 1920-1965, with the bulk of the records spanning the active years of the FAP: 1935-1942. The collection comprises 12.4 linear feet of photographic prints and negatives, including photos of FAP artists and the artwork created by them, and other activities of the FAP in communities throughout New York City and other states. Photographers include Andrew Herman, Sol Horn, David Robbins, Leo Seltzer, and others.
Artist files comprise three-quarters of the collection and consist primarily of photographs of artwork, as well as scattered photos of artists at work, including: Charles Alston, Luis Arenal, Richmond Barthe, John Benson, Andrew Berger, Lucille Blanch, Lucienne Bloch, Ilya Bolotowsky, Luise Brann, Selma Burke, Letterio Calapai, Eugene Chodorow, Francis Criss, Stuart Davis, Adolf Dehn, Virginia Dehn, Jose de Rivera, George Pearse Ennis, Philip Evergood, Eugenie Gershoy, Bertram Goodman, Arshile Gorky, Marion Greenwood, Philip Guston, Donal Hord, Joseph Hovell, William Karp, Yasuo Kuniyoshi, Edward Laning, Julian Levi, Audrey McMahon, Elizabeth Olds, Anton Refregier, Will Shuster, William Zorach, and others.
The remainder of the collection consists of files documenting related activities and programs of the FAP, arranged by subject. The bulk of these files document the activities of the New York City FAP, including free art classes and art exhibitions for adults and children, exhibitions at the Harlem Art Center, and the work of FAP branches including the Easel Division, the Graphic Arts Division, and the Poster Division.
Other subjects documented include federal and community art centers in eleven states, most extensively Washington State; other WPA projects such as the Federal Theater Project, the Federal Music Project, and the Federal Writers' Project; buildings decorated with FAP artwork; art processes as demonstrated by FAP artists; special events; and people involved with the FAP, including director Holger Cahill.
One folder contains images that appear to have been taken by Berenice Abbott for the exhibition Changing New York (1935), for the Museum of the City of New York in collaboration with the WPA.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 2 series:
Missing Title
Series 1: Artist Files, circa 1920-1965 (Boxes 1-24; 9.6 linear feet)
Series 2: Subject Files, 1934-1956 (Boxes 25-32; 2.8 linear feet)
Children's art; Photography; Art -- United States -- Exhibitions -- Photographs; Art -- United States -- Study and teaching -- Photographs; Art centers; Federal aid to the public welfare -- Photographs; Theater and state -- United States -- Photographs; Music and state -- United States -- Photographs; Federal aid to the arts -- Photographs; Art -- Technique; Artists -- United States -- Photographs; Photographs; Art -- Exhibitions; Latino and Latin American artists; Art -- Study and teaching; African American artists; Programs (organizations); Agencies; Berger, Andrew; Blanch, Lucile, 1895-1981; Kuniyoshi, Yasuo, 1889-1953; Guston, Philip, 1913-1980; Olds, Elizabeth, 1896-1991; Harlem Art Center; Goodman, Bertram, 1904-1988; Criss, Francis, 1901-1973; Benson, John Howard, 1901-1956; Dehn, Virginia E. (Virginia Engleman), 1922-2005; Greenwood, Marion, 1909-1970; Chodorow, Eugene (1910-2000); Refregier, Anton, 1905-; Ennis, George Pearse, d. 1936; Federal Writers' Project (U.S.) -- Photographs; United States. Work Projects Administration; McMahon, Audrey, 1900?-1981; Arenal, Luis; Herman, Andrew; Horn, Sol; Barthé, Richmond, 1901-1989; Robbins, David; Seltzer, Leo, 1916-; Brann, Louise, 1906-; Levi, Julian E. (Julian Edwin), 1900-1982; Laning, Edward, 1906-1981; Gorky, Arshile, 1904-1948; Zorach, William, 1887-1966; Calapai, Letterio, 1902-1993; Karp, William, 1905-; Hovell, Joseph, 1897-; Davis, Stuart, 1892-1964; United States. Works Progress Administration; Burke, Selma, 1900-; Dehn, Adolf, 1895-1968; Shuster, Will; Evergood, Philip, 1901-1973; Bloch, Lucienne, 1909-1999; Gershoy, Eugenie, 1901?-1983 or 6; Federal Art Project. Graphic Arts Division; Federal Art Project (N.Y.); De Rivera, José Ruiz, 1904-1985; Hord, Donal, 1902-1966; Federal Art Project. Easel Division; Federal Art Project. Poster Division; Bolotowsky, Ilya, 1907-1981; Federal Art Project (Wash.); Alston, Charles Henry, 1907-1977; Cahill, Holger, 1887-1960; Federal Theatre Project (U.S.) -- Photographs; Federal Music Project (U.S.) -- Photographs; Abbott, Berenice, 1898-1991; Federal Art Project -- Photographs
- Artist Files, circa 1920-1965; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 9.6 Linear feet Boxes 1-24
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists primarily of photographs of artwork produced by FAP artists, in addition to scattered photographs of artists and other individuals engaged in FAP work, or attending FAP events. An attempt has been made to date photographs using dates provided on the back of the photos where these exist, although it should be noted that those dates may not accurately indicate the date on which copy prints were produced. In the case of undated material a date of "circa 1935-circa 1942" is assigned to the folder, since it can reasonably be assumed that most photographs were taken within that time period. A few items pre-date or post-date the existence of the FAP.
  Arrangement note
  Photographs are arranged alphabetically by name of artist. Folder notes indicate when a folder contains photos of the artist.
  Existence and Location of Copies
  Series is scanned in entirety with the exception of duplicate copy prints, negatives of existing copy prints, and blank versos of photographs.
  - Abbate, Paolo S., 1931-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abbenseth, William, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abelman, Ida, 1936-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abernathy, Inez, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abramovitz, Albert, circa 1935-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Abramson, Hershel, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adams, Charles; Adams, Kenneth Miller, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adler, Fred, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adler, Joseph, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Afroyim, Beys, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Aguado, Hyman, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ajay, Abraham, 1939, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Albrizio, Humbert, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Albro, Maxine, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alexandrovich, Albert, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alger, John, 1937-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alland, Alexander, 1936-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Allen, John, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Aloisi, Anna, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alshets, Simon, 1936-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
    includes photo of Alshets, 1938 August
  - Alston, Charles, circa 1938-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
    includes photos of Alston, 1939
  - Ambellan, Harold, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Amero, Emilio, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Ames, Grace Greenwood, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Anchel, Harold, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Anderson, Carlos, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Angel, Rifka, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Angell, Blanche, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Annunziata, Nicoli, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Arcamonte, Humbert, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Archer, Robert, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Arenal, Luis, circa 1936-circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
    includes photos of Arenal, 1936
  - Arkavi, M. H., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Arms, John Taylor, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Arnold, A. Grant, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Artman, Jean, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Ashe, Edmund, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Ashley, James, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Atkins, Florence Elizabeth, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Atkinson, John Ingliss, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Ault, George C., 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Austin, Darrel, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Austin, Ralph, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Ausubel, Sheva, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 44)
    includes photos of Ausubel, 1937-1938
  - Avery, Frances, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Avery, Milton, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Baccante, Enzo, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Bacharach, Herman I., 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Bagis, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Bahnmuller, W., circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Baizerman, Eugenie, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bakos, Josef, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Ball, F. Carlton, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Bannarn, Henry Wilmer, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 54)
    includes photos of Bannarn
  - Barbarossa, Theodore Cotillo, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Barbu, Elena, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bard, Philip, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Barela, Patrocino, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
    includes photos of Barela, circa 1936
  - Barnet, Will, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Barone, Antonio, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Barr, N., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Barrows, Charles, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Barthe, Richmond, 1939, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
    includes photo of Barthe, 1941
  - Barto, Emily Newton, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
    includes photo of Barto, 1937 October
  - Bartsch, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bateman, John, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bates, Isabel, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
    includes photo of Bates
  - Bates, Kenneth, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Baum, Mark, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Baum, Max, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Baumann, Gustave, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Baumbach, Harold, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bawler, H. J., 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bayard, Lucy (Lucie), 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Baziotes, William, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Beach, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Beach, Beata, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Beauchamp, John W., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Beck, Morris, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Becker, Frederick W., 1936-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Becker, Samuel, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bedford, Enea, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bekker, David, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Bell, Clara Louise, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bell, Enid, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Belsor, L. H., 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Beman, Roff, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Bengelsdont, Rosalind, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Benn, Ben, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Bennett, Rainey, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Ben-Shmuel, Ahron, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Benson, John, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 38)
    includes photo of Benson, 1938 May
  - Bentley, John W., 1938, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Bentz, John, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Berger, Andrew, circa 1935-circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 41)
    includes photo of Berger, 1936 April
  - Bergere, Frederick, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Berlow, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Berman, Sarah, 1936-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Berman, Saul, circa 1940-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Berninghaus, Charles T., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Bernstein, Morris Louis, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Biafora, Enea, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Biddle, George, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 49)
    photo of Biddle, 1936
  - Bigelow, Barbara, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Billings, Henry, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Bishop, Isabel, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Bissell, Cleveland, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Bisttram, Emil, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Bjorn, Aleth C., 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Black, Harold, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Blanch, Arnold, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Blanch, Lucille, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 58)
    includes photo of Blanch, 1940 October
  - Blazy, Sterling, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Bloch, Julius, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bloch, Lucienne, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
    includes photos of Bloch, circa 1938
  - Block, Irving, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Block, Paul, circa 1935-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Blumenau, Lili, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Blumenfeld, Maurice, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bodin, Paul, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bolotowsky, Ilya, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
    includes photos of Bolotowsky, circa 1938-circa 1939
  - Bolton, Clarence, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bonamico, S., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Booth, Cameron, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Borghi, Guido, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Borne, Mortimer, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Botke, Jessie Arms, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Botts, Hugh Pearce, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bouché, Louis, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bowden, Harry, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Bowes, Julian, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Bowler, Harold, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Boyd, Byron B., 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Boyd, Douglas, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Boylos, Selma, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Boynton, Ray, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Brackman, Robert, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brandfield, Dayton, 1938-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brann, Louise, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
    includes photos of Brann, circa 1936
  - Braun, Clayton, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Breidvik, Mons, circa 1936-circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Breinin, Raymond, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Brennecke, Muriel, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Breslow, Louis, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Brigante, Nicholas, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Briggs, Judson, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Brindesi, Olympio, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Brisman, Hyman, circa 1935-circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Brockman, Ann, 1936-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Brodsky, George, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Brody, Laws, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Unidentified Artist, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Identification of artist in photographs as Manuel Bromberg, noted in verso inscriptions, is incorrect. Artist in photographs is unidentified.
  - Brooks, Eve, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Brooks, James, circa 1937-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 41)
    includes photo of Brooks, 1940 August
  - Brown, Helen, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Brown, Robert A., 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Browne, Byron, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Bruce, Edward, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Brussel-Smith, Bernard, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Buck, Bennett, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Burchfield, Charles, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Burke, David, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Burke, Selma, circa 1925-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 50)
    includes photos of Burke
  - Burlin, Paul, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Burlingame, Dennis, circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Burliuk, David D., 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Burstyn, Jerome, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Busa, Peter, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Buzzelli, Joseph A., 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Byer, Alexander, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Byron, Redman, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Caesar, Doris Porter, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Caffey, Neva, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Calapai, Letterio, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
    includes photos of Calapai, circa 1937
  - Campanella, Vincent, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Campbell, Alice, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Campbell, Blendon, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Canadé, Vincent, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cardona, Marguerite, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Caredio, Primo, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cartaino, Paolo, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Cash, Harold, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Cassidy, Gerald, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Catenaro, Armand, circa 1939-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Cavallon, Giorgio, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Cederquist, Arthur E., circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Celentano, Daniel, circa 1937-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)